== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Raj:)Oh, my God, I just got it.
(Raj:)Fun onions...
(Raj:)Funyuns.
(Raj:)Hold on.
(Raj:)Is that a wobble?
(Raj:)Yes.
(Raj:)That's definitely
a gravitational wobble.
(Cleaner:)Uh, sorry,
I could come back.
(Raj:)Oh, no, it's okay.
I-I just found a wobble.
(Cleaner:)Oh, do I need a mop?
(Raj:)It's a gravitational wobble.
(Raj:)It could be a sign
of an extrasolar planet
(Raj:)that may contain life
and someday be named after me.
(Cleaner:)Oh... well, if it has life,
(Cleaner:)maybe it already has a name,
huh?
(Raj:)Yeah, but it's probably
difficult to pronounce.
(Cleaner:)What is your name?
Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
(Cleaner:)You think it would be
(Cleaner:)more difficult than that?
(Raj:)Good point.
(Raj:)And you are?
Oh, uh, Issabella Maria
Concepcion.